Hello everyone, I am from the technical department.
안녕하세요 여러분, 저는 기술부서에서 왔습니다.
Come over and fix it up a bit.
오셔서 좀 고쳐보세요.
Deputy Director Wang’s computer
왕 부국장의 컴퓨터
what is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
What went wrong this time?
이번에는 무엇이 잘못됐나요?
It took so long.
너무 오래 걸렸어요.
Just looking for a minute.
잠시만 찾고 있습니다.
See if there is
있는지 확인해보세요
New system error.
새로운 시스템 오류입니다.
your technical department
귀하의 기술 부서
Quite responsible.
꽤 책임감이 있습니다.
always come
항상 오세요
Come and check the computer
와서 컴퓨터를 확인해 보세요
Who has repaired this computer before?
이전에 이 컴퓨터를 수리한 사람은 누구입니까?
I do not remember.
기억이 안나요.
Did you discover anything?
뭔가 발견하셨나요?
quickly.
빠르게.
Later, Deputy Director Wang
나중에 왕 부국장
will return.
돌아올 것이다.
Soon, soon.
곧 곧.
yellow.
노란색.
Is this week over yet?
이번주가 벌써 끝났나요?
already.
이미.
this.
이것.
follow me.
나를 따르라.
Come on, sit down.
자, 앉으세요.
sit down.
앉아.
this week
이번 주
very good.
매우 좋은.
You haven't seen it yet
아직 본 적 ​​없으시죠?
Didn't see it.
그것을 보지 못했습니다.
Seeing you working so hard,
열심히 일하는 모습을 보니,
You can't go wrong.
당신은 잘못 갈 수 없습니다.
I have been paying attention to you these days.
나는 요즘 당신에게 관심을 기울이고 있습니다.
Who are you
누구세요
I've seen it before.
나는 그것을 본 적이 있다.
I know.
알아요.
Director Huang arranged for you here
황 감독이 당신을 위해 여기에 준비했습니다
to train you.
당신을 훈련시키기 위해.
If you are interested
관심이 있으시면
supervisor position,
감독직,
We can be a couple.
우리는 커플이 될 수 있어요.
I will fully support
전폭적으로 지지하겠습니다
Your job.
작업.
After you finish speaking,
말을 마친 후,
I'm a little confused.
조금 혼란 스럽습니다.
I know.
알아요.
you two
너희 둘
Don't want to be too obvious.
너무 뻔한 것을 원하지 마십시오.
How do you know Huang?
황씨는 어떻게 아시나요?
Director Huang belongs to my father?
황 감독은 우리 아버지의 것인가요?
when I'm gone
내가 없을 때
For Director Huang,
황 감독에게
I've seen you.
나는 당신을 보았다.
This month’s assessment is ahead of schedule.
이번 달 평가는 예정보다 앞당겨졌습니다.
I will recommend you.
나는 당신을 추천합니다.
No, no.
아니 아니.
My father disliked this the most.
아버지는 이것을 가장 싫어하셨다.
You recommended me as soon as I came here.
여기 오자마자 추천해주셨어요.
He must be counting
그 사람이 계산을 하고 있는 게 틀림없어
You are a sycophant.
당신은 아첨꾼입니다.
no.
아니요.
That was not what I meant.
내 말은 그런 뜻이 아니었습니다.
I mean,
내 말은,
me and my father
나와 내 아버지
Prefer humility.
겸손을 선호하십시오.
Such a good opportunity,
이렇게 좋은 기회,
Better to give it to someone else.
다른 사람에게 주는 것이 더 좋습니다.
well.
잘.
Oh yes.
바로 이거 야.
I remember you once said,
당신이 한 번 말했던 것을 기억합니다.
Go and repair the leader’s computer.
가서 리더의 컴퓨터를 수리하세요.
Must be reported.
신고해야 합니다.
I have read the maintenance instructions
유지관리 지침을 읽었습니다.
Deputy Director Wang’s computer
왕 부국장의 컴퓨터
You are the one who protects him
그 사람을 지켜주는 사람은 바로 당신이에요
I...
나...
It's written in the maintenance notes.
유지보수 노트에 적혀 있습니다.
but i guess
하지만 내 생각엔
You're not going alone, are you?
너 혼자 가는 건 아니지, 그렇지?
Normally I don't need to go.
보통은 갈 필요가 없어요.
Unless something is important,
중요한 일이 아니라면,
I'll take care of it.
내가 처리할게.
you remember
당신은 기억한다
who goes
누가 가나
Xiang.
샹.
daytime,
낮,
Usually sunny.
보통 맑음.
Others are during the day
다른 사람들은 낮에
go to eat
먹으러 가다
Or do something personal.
아니면 개인적인 일을 하세요.
There is only sunshine.
햇빛만 있습니다.
Basically it's daytime.
기본적으로 낮이에요.
Xiang Yang.
샹양.
Shi Tou.
시 토우.
You make arrangements first.
먼저 준비를 하세요.
CCTV footage from today.
오늘 CCTV 영상입니다.
OK
좋아요
how?
어떻게?
Check CCTV.
CCTV를 확인해 보세요.
Try to compare with these photos.
이 사진들과 비교해 보세요.
It feels like clothes
옷같은 느낌이에요
Has not changed much.
많이 변하지 않았습니다.
of.
의.
look.
바라보다.
His clothes used to be a bit stiff.
그의 옷은 좀 뻣뻣했어요.
The style you see now.
지금 보시는 스타일.
Youth is more agile.
젊음은 더 민첩합니다.
More attention.
더 많은 관심.
I realized
나는 깨달았다
After being with Xiao Yi,
샤오이와 함께한 후,
She is very pretty.
그녀가 너무 예뻐요.
here.
여기.
He also got a new pair of glasses.
그는 또한 새로운 안경을 받았습니다.
It was given to him by Xiao Yi.
그것은 Xiao Yi가 그에게 준 것입니다.
If you look at the time,
시간을 보면,
is a new devotional book.
새로운 묵상서이다.
When this was confirmed,
이 사실이 확인되자,
Youchen.
Youchen.
Just think of a way.
방법을 생각해 보세요.
Examine Zhu Yan's glasses.
Zhu Yan의 안경을 살펴보세요.
But usually
하지만 보통
People who wear glasses for a long time
안경을 오랫동안 착용하시는 분
Should I go home?
집에 가야하나요?
Just took off your glasses?
방금 안경을 벗었나요?
Also when taking a shower and sleeping.
샤워할 때나 잠잘 때도 마찬가지다.
And while exercising.
그리고 운동하는 동안.
He didn't take off his glasses.
그는 안경을 벗지 않았습니다.
Replacement Plan B.
교체 계획 B.
Lift your right leg.
오른쪽 다리를 들어 올리세요.
Come between the two hands.
두 손 사이로 오세요.
Hold your ears between your hands and lift them up.
두 손으로 귀를 잡고 들어 올리세요.
Put your hands together.
손을 모으십시오.
Right shoulder finds knee.
오른쪽 어깨가 무릎을 찾습니다.
Okay, take your hands back.
좋아, 손을 뒤로 빼세요.
Choose what's convenient.
편리한 것을 선택하세요.
lie.
거짓말하다.
Release your hands.
손을 놓으십시오.
Palms facing up.
손바닥이 위를 향하게 합니다.
The body is completely relaxed.
몸이 완전히 이완됩니다.
Relax
안심하다
in your body.
당신의 몸에.
Muscle tension.
근육 긴장.
Feel the blood in your toes.
발가락의 피를 느껴보세요.
Slowly flow into the body.
천천히 몸 속으로 흘러 들어갑니다.
only.
오직.
Little feet.
작은 발.
Licking the front.
앞을 핥는 중.
and back muscle tension.
그리고 등 근육 긴장.
Meditation is only 10 minutes.
명상은 단 10분만 하세요.
There are eight minutes left, you have to hurry up.
8분 남았으니 서둘러야 합니다.
There is a mini camera.
미니 카메라가 있습니다.
There is a memory card.
메모리카드가 있습니다.
All quote data
모든 견적 데이터
data bidding,
데이터 입찰,
All spies can escape.
모든 스파이는 탈출할 수 있습니다.
[record information]
[기록정보]
This has been noted.
이것이 언급되었습니다.
Make a copy.
사본을 만드세요.
Come on, there are still 4 minutes.
자, 아직 4분 남았습니다.
1 minute left, hurry up.
1분 남았으니 서두르세요.
Completed.
완전한.
quickly.
빠르게.
Be careful.
조심하세요.
OK
좋아요
Now stand up slowly.
이제 천천히 일어서세요.
Wake up your body.
몸을 깨워라.
sorry.
죄송합니다.
Who got the wrong glasses?
안경을 잘못 쓴 사람은 누구입니까?
I accidentally took it.
실수로 가져갔습니다.
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
excuse me. OK
실례합니다. 좋아요
Thank you for your sacrifices in this class.
이 수업에서 여러분의 희생에 감사드립니다.
Okay, get out of class is over.
자, 수업 종료는 끝났습니다.
Attention, one team.
주목하세요, 한 팀입니다.
Xiao Yi datang.
샤오이 다탕.
Xiao Yi.
샤오이.
Come in for a while.
잠시 들어와 보세요.
We've checked.
우리는 확인했습니다.
Kacamata Zhu Yan
카카마타 주얀
Specially designed.
특별히 디자인되었습니다.
Has photo taking function.
사진 촬영 기능이 있습니다.
Insert the memory card.
메모리 카드를 삽입하세요.
There are several stored in it
그 안에 여러개 저장되어 있어요
Several tender documents have been translated.
여러 입찰 문서가 번역되었습니다.
Fortunately,
다행스럽게도,
The last card of the deal is important.
거래의 마지막 카드가 중요합니다.
Not submitted yet.
아직 제출되지 않았습니다.
In the hands of the translation team.
번역팀의 손에 있습니다.
Because of Zhu Yan’s glasses
주옌의 안경 때문에
Specially made
특별히 제작된
Specially restored.
특별히 복원되었습니다.
So you can avoid it.
그래서 당신은 그것을 피할 수 있습니다.
Security check.
보안 검색.
We have the secret recipe,
비밀 레시피가 있는데,
Then we can release the arrow.
그런 다음 화살표를 놓을 수 있습니다.
Now seize Zhu Yan,
이제 Zhu Yan을 붙잡으세요.
Not interesting.
흥미롭지 않습니다.
Xiao Yi.
샤오이.
And Boss Zhang behind him.
그리고 그 뒤에는 장 보스(Boss Zhang)가 있습니다.
That's the point.
그게 요점입니다.
So, we have to find a way
그러니 우리는 방법을 찾아야 해요
In addition to ensuring standard safety,
표준적인 안전을 보장하는 것 외에도
It also prevents the enemy from being surprised.
또한 적이 놀라는 것을 방지합니다.
If he wants standards,
그가 표준을 원한다면,
Give him a standard.
그에게 기준을 제시하세요.
Just follow the game.
게임을 따라가시면 됩니다.
correct.
옳은.
partner.
파트너.
I just came.
나 막 왔어.
What's delicious here?
여기 뭐가 맛있나요?
This spicy hotpot tastes terrible.
이 매운 전골은 맛이 정말 끔찍해요.
Let me waste my time waiting in line.
줄을 서서 기다리며 시간을 낭비하게 해주세요.
Been in line for a long time.
오랫동안 줄을 섰습니다.
All is well.
모든 것이 잘되었습니다.
explain.
설명하다.
Sitting in the office every day,
매일 사무실에 앉아서
Sit until I get a headache.
머리가 아플 때까지 앉아 계세요.
Eyes hurt, neck hurts.
눈도 아프고 목도 아프다.
Your pillow is great.
당신의 베개는 훌륭합니다.
where to buy?
구입처?
internet.
인터넷.
able
할 수 있는
Send me a link?
나에게 링크를 보내 주시겠어요?
OK
좋아요
In your opinion, if I were
당신 생각에는 만약 내가 그랬다면
Go to work, fish and play games,
출근도 하고, 낚시도 하고, 게임도 하고,
Will the manager notice me?
매니저가 나를 알아챌까?
of.
의.
Have you had any recently?
최근에 그런 일이 있었나요?
Fun game?
재미있는 게임?
You recommended it to me.
당신은 나에게 그것을 추천했습니다.
I finished eating.
나는 식사를 마쳤다.
No. Are you done?
아니요. 끝났나요?
Be careful.
조심하세요.
Who is this?
누구세요?
It's hard to say.
말하기가 어렵습니다.
where are you going?
어디 가세요?
bathroom.
화장실.
you go?
너가?
No.
아니요.
It's you.
당신이에요.
Sea Knight.
바다 기사.
It's all over.
모든 끝났어.
The mission is finally over.
드디어 임무가 끝났습니다.
I was a little worried before.
예전에는 조금 걱정이 됐어요.
I told you not to worry.
나는 걱정하지 말라고 말했다.
I should have believed you.
나는 당신을 믿었어야 했어요.
certainly.
틀림없이.
this new phone
이 새 전화기
how?
어떻게?
reasonable.
합리적인.
how much does it cost?
비용이 얼마나 드나요?
No money is needed.
돈이 필요하지 않습니다.
Give it leadership.
리더십을 발휘하세요.
Including work-related injuries.
업무상 부상도 포함됩니다.
very good.
매우 좋은.
Protagonist?
주역?
no.
아니요.
suspicious.
의심스러운.
this?
이것?
Yaoyao specially brought it to you.
Yaoyao가 특별히 가져왔습니다.
It is said to help with sleep.
숙면에 도움을 준다고 합니다.
Thanks.
감사해요.
How does he feel?
그의 기분은 어떠 할까?
It is nothing special.
특별한 것은 아닙니다.
But my phone did change.
그런데 내 휴대폰이 바뀌었다.
What else are you worried about?
또 어떤 걱정이 있나요?
Be careful and optimistic.
조심하고 낙관하십시오.
you
너
Be very careful.
정말 조심하세요.
Never optimistic.
결코 낙관적이지 않습니다.
You are the exact opposite.
당신은 정반대입니다.
Incidentally,
그런데,
When will Xi Jinping come back?
시진핑은 언제 돌아올 것인가?
Let him know.
그에게 알려주세요.
haven't seen you for a long time.
오랫동안 당신을 보지 못했습니다.
Miss you a lot.
당신을 많이 그리워.
Don't talk nonsense.
말도 안되는 소리를하지 마십시오.
Say no more.
더 말하지 마.
look at this.
이거 봐요.
Xiang Yang is also a gamer.
Xiang Yang도 게이머입니다.
Deputy Director Wang’s computer
왕 부국장의 컴퓨터
Isn’t it already implanted?
이미 이식된거 아닌가요?
Trojan virus?
트로이 목마 바이러스?
first,
첫째,
I don't think he did.
나는 그가 그랬다고 생각하지 않습니다.
This person is visible
이 사람이 보입니다
Looks silly.
어리석은 것 같습니다.
He is not fit to be a spy.
그는 스파이가 되기에 적합하지 않습니다.
He is also a player.
그는 또한 선수이다.
How well do you know him?
당신은 그를 얼마나 잘 알고 있나요?
as far as I know,
내가 아는 한,
This person usually
이 사람은 평소에
He is a one-dimensional otaku.
그는 1차원적인 오타쿠이다.
I have always been in contact with him.
나는 항상 그와 연락을 취해왔습니다.
No.
아니요.
need help?
도움이 필요하다?
You know nothing about otakus.
당신은 오타쿠에 대해 아무것도 모릅니다.
Family man tricks.
패밀리맨의 트릭.
I'm relatively skilled.
나는 상대적으로 능숙합니다.
Fishing is not the point.
낚시가 요점이 아닙니다.
Your focus is on confirming his identity.
당신의 초점은 그의 신원을 확인하는 것입니다.
and found the boss.
그리고 사장님을 찾았습니다.
I got you.
나는 당신을 얻었다.
In the world of special forces missions,
특수부대 임무의 세계에서는
I am the preferred agent.
나는 우선 대리인입니다.
what else?
또 뭐야?
flower.
꽃.
I want to discuss something with you.
나는 당신과 뭔가 논의하고 싶습니다.
Why do I have a bad feeling?
왜 기분이 좋지 않습니까?
Before,
전에,
Didn't I sell you a hot air balloon?
내가 당신에게 열기구를 팔지 않았나요?
I want to make up for it.
나는 그것을 만회하고 싶다.
What?
무엇?
If you're flirting with a woman, there's no need to talk about it.
여자를 유혹한다면 그것에 대해 이야기할 필요가 없습니다.
I really want to soak.
정말 담그고 싶어요.
But a man.
하지만 남자.
Invisible.
보이지 않는.
Very wide.
매우 넓습니다.
No more kidding.
더 이상 농담하지 마세요.
I have important things.
나에게는 중요한 것들이 있습니다.
Serious business?
진지한 사업?
Maybe there is a connection
어쩌면 연결이있을 수도 있습니다
You asked me for help two days ago?
이틀 전에 나한테 도움을 요청하셨나요?
Don't be afraid to join
두려워하지 말고 참여하세요
Heretical organization?
이단조직?
Later people cheat again.
나중에 사람들은 다시 바람을 피운다.
Are you kidding me?
농담하는 거야?
People like me,
나 같은 사람들은,
Can other people cheat on you?
다른 사람들이 당신을 속일 수 있나요?
This is not necessarily true.
이것은 반드시 사실은 아닙니다.
Not your partner?
파트너가 아니신가요?
deceived you
당신을 속였습니다
Eat less, you have to learn.
적게 먹고, 배워야 합니다.
young adults.
젊은 성인.
That's it, that's it, that's it.
그게 다야, 그게 다야, 그게 다야.
I know.
알아요.
Isn't it just a hot air balloon?
그냥 열기구 아닌가요?
And I asked you to criticize me.
그리고 나는 당신에게 나를 비판하라고 요청했습니다.
To sell or not to sell? You just open the price.
팔 것인가, 팔지 않을 것인가? 가격만 공개하면 됩니다.
What is the opening price?
개장 가격은 얼마입니까?
Do you still have money?
아직도 돈이 있나요?
Look at your clothes.
옷을 좀 보세요.
Groom early.
일찍 신랑.
Do you like rich people?
당신은 부자를 좋아합니까?
It has to be a real family.
진짜 가족이어야 해요.
OK
좋아요
leave.
떠나다.
Huang Dana.
황 다나.
Sea Knight.
바다 기사.
Have you brought anything?
뭐 가져오셨나요?
The hot air balloon you want.
당신이 원하는 열기구.
Thanks.
감사해요.
Do you need any other equipment?
다른 장비가 필요합니까?
no thanks.
고맙지 만 사양 할게.
Do you like it?
당신은 그것을 좋아합니까?
criticize.
흠잡다.
Come on, I'll take you to see something.
어서, 뭔가 보러 데려갈게.
look.
바라보다.
Very cool.
아주 멋지다.
Ayo.
아요.
very beautiful.
매우 아름답습니다.
So sad.
너무 슬퍼.
Sir, madam.
선생님, 부인.
It's very romantic here.
여기는 매우 낭만적입니다.
Can I take your photo?
사진을 찍어도 될까요?
certainly.
틀림없이.
let me see.
좀 보자.
reasonable.
합리적인.
Thanks.
감사해요.
OK
좋아요
Ayo.
아요.
Look over there.
저기 봐.
look.
바라보다.
Isn’t it great here?
여기 정말 좋지 않나요?
So sad.
너무 슬퍼.
It's very nice there.
거기는 아주 좋아요.
Do you like it?
당신은 그것을 좋아합니까?
Very beautiful view.
매우 아름다운 전망.
correct.
옳은.
this is my first time
이번이 처음이야
Watch the night view from such a high place.
이렇게 높은 곳에서 야경을 감상해보세요.
I remember you once said
당신이 한 번 말했던 걸 기억해요
Want to travel in a hot air balloon.
열기구를 타고 여행하고 싶어요.
I'll make you feel
느끼게 해줄게
in the game.
게임에서.
I like it very much.
나는 그것을 아주 많이 좋아.
Thanks.
감사해요.
Remember my wish.
내 소원을 기억해 주세요.
do not know when
언제인지 모른다
can take you there
당신을 거기로 데려갈 수 있어요
trip
여행
[In real life. ]
[현실에서. ]
We will meet one day.
우리는 언젠가 만날 것입니다.
I'm ready for you.
난 준비 됐어.
So sad.
너무 슬퍼.
Nice to meet you.
만나서 반가워요.
Incidentally,
그런데,
I already handed over the gold coins
난 이미 금화를 넘겨줬어요
gold.
금.
We made a lot of money again.
우리는 또 많은 돈을 벌었습니다.
Fortunately you are here this time.
다행히 이번에는 당신이 여기에 있습니다.
It does not matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
I know you can do this.
나는 당신이 이것을 할 수 있다는 것을 알고 있습니다.
after all you are
결국 당신은
in my heart.
내 마음 속에.
Now if you
이제 당신이
by my side.
내 곁에.
Although we can't meet each other,
비록 서로 만날 수는 없지만
But our hearts are together.
그러나 우리의 마음은 함께 있습니다.
Are you leaving me?
나를 떠나는 건가요?
No.
아니요.
As long as we can continue to work together,
우리가 계속 함께 일할 수 있는 한,
mission accomplished,
임무 완수,
I will always be by your side.
난 항상 당신 곁에있을 것입니다.
Never separate.
절대 분리하지 마십시오.
Enter.
입력하다.
Why are you here again?
왜 또 여기 왔어?
Find someone for me.
나를 위한 사람을 찾아보세요.
The girl in this photo.
이 사진 속의 소녀.
Namanya Xiao Bai.
나만야 샤오바이.
He also said this was not flirting with a woman.
그는 또한 이것이 여자를 유혹하는 것이 아니라고 말했습니다.
Is this your new girlfriend?
이 사람이 네 새 여자친구야?
No.
아니요.
Help you check this and that every day.
매일 이것저것 확인하도록 도와주세요.
Annoying.
짜증 나는.
If today
만약 오늘
Didn't tell me clearly,
나한테는 명확하게 말하지 않았는데,
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
I won't
나는하지 않을 것이다
Help you again.
다시 도와주세요.
I will tell you.
난 당신을 말할 것이다.
I
나
actually join
실제로 가입하다
Mysterious organization.
신비한 조직.
What organization?
무슨 조직?
This name...
이 이름...
I can't tell you.
나는 당신에게 말할 수 없습니다.
But our organization
하지만 우리 조직은
Specializes in combating various criminal activities.
다양한 범죄 행위에 맞서 싸우는 데 특화되어 있습니다.
I just showed you.
방금 보여줬어요.
What happened to the girl in the photo?
사진 속 소녀에게는 무슨 일이 있었던 걸까요?
He's in the game.
그는 게임에 참여하고 있습니다.
in the game.
게임에서.
They all have groups.
그들은 모두 그룹을 가지고 있습니다.
Swindling money and cheating women.
돈을 사기도 하고 여자를 속이기도 합니다.
You know how to use everything, don't you?
당신은 모든 것을 사용하는 방법을 알고 있지 않습니까?
Is there such an organization?
그런 조직이 있나요?
Why didn't I hear it?
왜 나는 그것을 듣지 못했습니까?
That mysterious organization
그 신비한 조직
It's impossible to let everyone know.
모두에게 알리는 것은 불가능합니다.
So who arranged this?
그럼 이걸 누가 준비한 걸까요?
Of course it's a gaming company.
물론 게임회사죠.
us?
우리를?
secret investigation
비밀 조사
Clean the gaming environment.
게임 환경을 청소하세요.
Eliminate criminal forces.
범죄 세력을 제거하십시오.
The game is also very clean.
게임도 매우 깔끔합니다.
think about it.
그것에 대해 생각해보세요.
If in this game
만약 이 게임에서
Everything is illegal,
다 불법이고,
It will definitely be cleaned up.
반드시 깨끗이 청소될 것입니다.
what would you do?
당신은 무엇을 하시겠습니까?
Also, I'm doing this job
게다가 나는 이 일을 하고 있어
Because of the high benefits and good treatment,
높은 혜택과 좋은 치료로 인해
I just finished it.
방금 끝냈어요.
It's such a good thing, don't invite me to play.
정말 좋은 일인데, 나한테 놀자고 하지 마세요.
Danger.
위험.
think about it.
그것에 대해 생각해보세요.
What do you face every day?
당신은 매일 무엇에 직면합니까?
Are evil people and liars.
악한 사람들이고 거짓말쟁이들이다.
you let them later
나중에 놔줘
by them again.
다시 그들에 의해.
how can i let you
내가 어떻게 당신을 허락할 수 있나요
Take the risk?
위험을 감수하다?
But don't worry.
하지만 걱정하지 마세요.
When eating delicious food and drinking spicy food,
맛있는 음식을 먹고 매운 음식을 마실 때,
Brother will never forget you.
형은 당신을 결코 잊지 않을 것입니다.
Can you help me this time?
이번에는 나를 도와주실 수 있나요?
What are they lying about?
그들은 무엇에 대해 거짓말을 하고 있는 걸까요?
Tools of fraud.
사기 도구.
we are struggling
우리는 어려움을 겪고 있습니다
Purchase equipment.
장비를 구입하세요.
They will deceive you.
그들은 당신을 속일 것입니다.
Can you hold on?
버틸 수 있나요?
of course not.
당연히 아니지.
so,
그래서,
We have to get rid of it.
우리는 그것을 제거해야 합니다.
In time, you will become the ultimate hero.
시간이 지나면 당신은 최고의 영웅이 될 것입니다.
Okay, I'll look into it right away.
알겠습니다. 바로 조사해 보겠습니다.
How long will it take to find it?
그것을 찾는 데 얼마나 걸릴까요?
Just over a minute,
1분 남짓,
They will cheat one more person.
그들은 또 한 사람을 속일 것입니다.
Latest tomorrow.
내일 늦어요.
You are more reliable.
당신은 더 신뢰할 수 있습니다.
Come home from get off work and eat.
퇴근하고 집에와서 먹어요.
Let's eat.
먹자.
I won't go, let's sleep for a while.
나 안 갈게, 좀 자자.
It was so unexpected.
정말 예상치 못한 일이었습니다.
Still an artistic young man.
아직도 예술적인 청년입니다.
quickly.
빠르게.
I am hungry.
나 배고파.
Then hurry up.
그럼 서둘러요.
Who arrived last? do the washing up.
마지막으로 도착한 사람은 누구입니까? 설거지 해.
I took this.
나는 이것을 가져갔다.
Why have you fallen so low?
왜 이렇게 낮아졌나요?
quickly.
빠르게.
I don't want to wash the dishes.
나는 설거지를하고 싶지 않습니다.
I want to wash the dishes for you.
나는 당신을 위해 설거지를 하고 싶습니다.
But I'm very sleepy.
그런데 너무 졸려요.
Who loses first?
누가 먼저 지는가?
Those who say they lose must wash the dishes.
졌다고 말하는 사람은 설거지를 해야 한다.
Who told you to go to the market?
누가 시장에 가라고 했나요?
At the vegetable market?
야채시장에서요?
I really can't stand it anymore and I want to sleep.
정말 더 이상 참을 수가 없어서 자고 싶어요.
Take a shower with me first and then go to bed.
먼저 나와 함께 샤워를 하고 잠자리에 드세요.
It's so kind of you.
정말 친절하시네요.
Then I am a koala
그럼 난 코알라야
tired.
피곤한.
Haven't slept since last night.
어젯밤부터 잠을 자지 못했습니다.
so far.
지금까지.
Forget it. Go to bed tomorrow.
잊어 버려. 내일 자러 가세요.
Sleep on the couch.
소파에서 자세요.
Half an hour is also useful.
30분도 유용합니다.
Forget it.
잊어 버려.
I'm hungry.
배고파요.
I made noodles for you.
나는 당신을 위해 국수를 만들었습니다.
Thanks.
감사해요.
Is there anything new?
새로운 게 있나요?
not yet.
아직 아님.
Zhu Yan
주얀
Live at Xiao Yi's house.
Xiao Yi의 집에 거주합니다.
He does this to make things easier.
그는 일을 더 쉽게 만들기 위해 이렇게 합니다.
Check captured data
캡처된 데이터 확인
Inside Zhu Yan’s glasses.
Zhu Yan의 안경 내부.
You thought it was the two of them
둘이서인 줄 알았지?
After the task is completed,
임무가 완료된 후,
Will they still be together?
그들은 여전히 ​​​​함께있을 것입니까?
Not appropriate.
적당하지 않은, 알맞지 않은.
correct.
옳은.
After the task is completed,
임무가 완료된 후,
We can't be together anymore.
우리는 더 이상 함께 할 수 없습니다.
What are you reading?
무엇을 읽습니까?
It's so boring that you fall asleep.
너무 지루해서 잠이 듭니다.
Peel it off the shelf.
선반에서 껍질을 벗기세요.
Helps you sleep.
잠을 잘 수 있도록 도와줍니다.
Dylan Thomas.
딜런 토마스.
What?
무엇?
Do you want to play the role of an artistic young man?
예술적인 청년 역할을 하고 싶나요?
Eat fruit.
과일을 먹습니다.
I picked up the phone first.
나는 먼저 전화기를 들었다.
The account was registered a year ago.
계정은 1년 전에 등록되었습니다.
Then when will he
그럼 그 사람은 언제쯤?
when?
언제?
in a month.
한 달 안에.
But I can't find the specific time.
하지만 구체적인 시간을 알 수 없습니다.
Does he have a gaming partner?
그 사람에게 게임 파트너가 있나요?
of.
의.
His name is "Sea Knight".
그의 이름은 "바다의 기사"입니다.
They have been working together for a year.
그들은 1년 동안 함께 일해 왔습니다.
It's a good fit.
잘 맞습니다.
This novice account is very strange.
이 초보자 계정은 매우 이상합니다.
Why is it strange?
왜 이상한가요?
Just a sea knight.
그냥 바다 기사.
So loyal.
정말 충성스럽습니다.
of.
의.
can you find it
찾을 수 있어?
The original photo?
원본 사진?
No.
아니요.
It's so hard.
너무 어려워요.
OK
좋아요
If so, please send the information to my email.
그렇다면 제 이메일로 정보를 보내주세요.
OK, thanks.
알았어 고마워.
Why are you looking at me?
왜 나를보고있어?
what is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
Honestly.
솔직히.
Suddenly I started reading English books again.
갑자기 영어책을 다시 읽기 시작했어요.
and went to the balcony to make phone calls.
그리고 전화를 하러 발코니로 나갔습니다.
did you do something
너 뭐라도 했어?
behind me?
내 뒤에?
No.
아니요.
I just made a new friend.
방금 새 친구를 사귀었어요.
new friend?
새 친구?
Is she a woman?
그 사람은 여자인가요?
how do you know?
어떻게 알아?
That's true.
그것은 사실이다.
I'm kidding.
농담이야.
Isn’t he my former gaming partner?
그 사람은 내 전 게임 파트너가 아니었나요?
Didn't I tell you?
내가 말하지 않았나요?
I do not believe.
난 믿지 않아.
look.
바라보다.
Are you still playing?
아직도 놀고 있나요?
If this is the equipment in the game
이게 게임 속 장비라면
I had to wait for him to give me cash.
나는 그가 나에게 현금을 줄 때까지 기다려야 했다.
OK
좋아요
I'll trust you for now.
지금은 당신을 믿을게요.
Do I still dare to lie to you?
내가 아직도 감히 당신에게 거짓말을 할 수 있습니까?
I went to the toilet.
나는 화장실에 갔다.
930726。
930726。
Thanks.
감사해요.
Do you like reading his poems?
그의 시를 읽는 걸 좋아하시나요?
WHO？
WHO?
Dylan Thomas.
딜런 토마스.
to be honest,
솔직히 말하자면,
Don't understand at all.
전혀 이해가 안 돼요.
I don’t understand why I put it in my bag.
왜 가방에 넣어두는지 이해가 안가네요.
hard to explain.
설명하기 어려운.
Being a man is not easy.
남자가되는 것은 쉽지 않습니다.
before you tell me,
나한테 말하기 전에,
program error,
프로그램 오류,
It's certainly worth paying attention to.
확실히 주목할 가치가 있습니다.
leader.
지도자.
We are all learning.
우리는 모두 배우고 있습니다.
OK, continue.
알겠습니다. 계속하세요.
This is the first time I see you smile.
당신이 웃는 모습을 처음 봤습니다.
I think
제 생각에는
Who are you
누구세요
very funny.
아주 재밌어요.
I feel the same way.
나도 같은 느낌이다.